살짝 다가와
can cross my borderline
널 따분하게 했던 everyday
흥미로운 덫을 던져줄게
뛰어들어봐 Just right now
Cuz I'm too spicy for your heart
ring the fire alarm
심장을 파고들어 넌
I'm too spicy
번지는 자극 속에 넌
바로 그 순간
또 다른 나를 발견해
I'm too spicy
too too I'm too spicy
Don't stop 겁내지 마
Hey bang bang 외쳐봐
I'm too spicy
Yeah I'm too spicy
You know that I
Don't stop 용기내봐
Hey next step myself
I'm too spicy
too too I'm too spicy
Tell me what you see
When you look at me
Cause I am a 10 out of 10 honestly
기세가 다른 move
너라도 아는 groove
But you keep wasting your time
경고해 난,
erase me
멀리 달아난
Hey 이젠 알겠니
원래부터 bad
I'm so bad honestly
So bad
전부 가질래
지금부턴 call you mine
Mine
도망칠 거면
Don't cross my borderline
Yeah yeah yeah
늘 뻔하기만 했던 everyday
이제 그만 rule을 벗어날 때
어렵지 않아
Just right now
Cause I'm too spicy for your heart
ring the fire alarm
심장을 파고들어 넌
I'm too spicy
Yeah I'm too spicy
번지는 자극 속에 넌
그 순간
또 다른 나를 발견해
He's too spicy
Too too
I'm too spicy
Ready
좀 더 강도를 높여
다음 다음 다음
One of a kind
우린 한계를 앞서 와 와 와
That's right
Cause I'm too spicy for your heart
ring the fire alarm
새로운 도전 끝에 넌
What do you know
I'm too spicy
변화할 시간이야 넌
지금 이 순간
So hot
또 다른 나를 찾아내
I'm too spicy
Too too
Don't stop
겁내지 마
Hey bang bang
외쳐봐
I'm too spicy
Yeah I'm too spicy
You know that I
Don't stop
용기내 봐
(hey), next step, myself
I'm too spicy
Too too too too spicy
Cause I'm
Yeah yeah yeah
Yeah I'm too spicy for your heart
마침내 번져오는 joy
(enjoy-joy-joy-joy)
Yeah I'm too spicy for your heart
I'm too spicy
Too too
For you